it strangely sitting in my moment about
gratitude looking up at the sky and this
brief um a lot about chemtrails aren't
even if chemtrails are real I watched a
documentary on them probably over a
decade ago and seem convincing like yeah
those are kind of sketchy I don't did
they last as long before I don't know
but that's not the idea for the app the
app is to follow chemtrails but I mean
that could be it's just not an idea that
I so much want to get behind to the
moment but a conspiracy theory website
where you can debunk it together or
figure it out together like what is the
truth behind chemtrails what is the
truth behind the 9/11 conspiracy and I
mean it's very related to the
information science app this would be
more than science because I don't know
if you can you can kind of I guess prove
or disprove 9/11 with science with
physics but the moon landing because I
don't know any conspiracy theory that
I've read there's some truth there like
it's like yeah who did flag doesn't move
on the moon and to be able to have a
space to discuss those things of what's
truth and what is been debunked and why
it's been debunked I would find really
useful one space that I can trust
because it's owned by all of us and in
purpose in
it's working for all of us so yeah how
does a poem about 34 conspiracy theory
website